Previously on...
《绝望的主妇》前情提要
A thief was confronted. well, maybe you'll feel
小偷原形毕露  也许你更愿意
Comfortable talking to a professional.
-和专家谈谈
a psychiatrist?
心理咨询师
Someone light me a cigar.
-给我点雪茄庆功吧
carlos hired a old girlfriend...
卡洛斯聘用了旧情人
And gaby hired a spy.
-而加布聘用了一个间谍
i talked to carlos. you're in!
我和卡洛斯谈过了  你被雇用了
Edie dug deeper into dave's past.
伊迪深入的发掘丈夫的过去
Killed three years ago-- car crash.
三年其死于车祸
That was his wife. give me that one.
那是他的妻子  给我吧
Their daughter died in the same crash.
他们的女儿也在车祸中亡故了
And dave's master plan...
-大卫的精心计划
you really think i make
你真的觉得
That much of a difference in mike's life?
我对麦克来说  有那么重要吗
If he ever lost you
如果失去你
It would destroy him.
他会痛不欲生
Entered its final phase.
进入了最后阶段
Uh, hi. is this the ranger station?
是卫林站吗
Well, i didn't know whether to call you or fish and game,
我不确定该向你们报告  还是向野生动物部门报告
But, uh, i think i saw some guys up at emerson woods
我似乎看到了一些非法狩猎者
Hunting illegally, and i got worried
进入了爱默生森林  我很担心
Because i know people like to go camping up there,
因为人们经常在那里露营
And i-i sure wouldn't want anyone to get hurt.
我不希望有人受伤
Oh. no, no need to thank me.
不不  没必要谢我
I'm just doing my part as a concerned citizen.
我只是在尽一个公民的责任
Bye now.
再见
Dave williams
大卫·威廉姆斯
Had been planning the murder for years.
煞费苦心的策划这场戏
And like all the best plans, it was a simple one.
就像其他的完美计划一样  很简单
First, he would guide
首先  他带着
Mike delfino and katherine mayfair
麦克·德尔非诺和凯瑟琳·梅菲尔
To a remote cabin.
到一个僻静的小屋
The next morning, he'd pretend to be asleep
次日早晨  当这对情侣出发去徒步时
As the two lovers left to go hiking.
他继续装睡
Dave would then grab the gun he'd carefully hidden...
然后大卫拿起事先小心藏好的枪
And start to follow his quarry.
开始追踪他的猎物
He'd wait until the two had paused for a moment
他耐心的等待
To catch their breaths.
直到他们停下歇息
And then he'd pull the trigger...
他便扣动扳机
Breaking the heart of the man who had killed his wife.
让这个杀害他妻子的男人  心痛欲绝
When the rangers arrived,
当护林人抵达
They would mention the reports of illegal hunte
他们会提及事前有人举报过的偷猎者
And dave would drive mike back home,
大卫就会开车和麦克一起回家
All the while enjoying his pain.
同时享受着麦克所受的折磨
Yes,
是的
Dave williams had come up With a very simple plan.
大卫·威廉姆斯策划了这个简单的计划
But as he was about to discover...
但他将会发现
Have you faxed this clipping to edie williams yet?
你还没有把这份报道传真给伊迪·威廉姆斯吗
Um, doing it right now.
马上就传
There is nothing simple...
策划杀人
About murder.
并不是简单的事
Life is full of nasty shocks...
生活中  充满了恶意的震惊
Unpleasant surprises that jolt our systems...
一些扰人的意外  扰乱人体系统
And cause our hearts to skip a beat.
一些  会吓得心跳漏了一拍
And these shocks always occur...
而且这样的震惊
Susan?
-苏珊
hey, karl.
嗨  卡尔
When we least expect them.
往往是不速之客
Karl.
卡尔
What are you doing here?
你怎么在这里
Well, i just enrolled evan.
我刚为埃文报名
And i was worried
我原本还担心
That we'd be out of each other's lives forever.
我们永远再也见不到了呢
Mm, lucky, lucky.
真是走运啊
What are you doing here?
-你怎么会在这里呢
i am an art teacher.
我是这里的艺术老师
Really? do they know that?
是吗  其他人知道吗
And now i'm ignoring you and moving on to evan.
我忽略你的话  和埃文聊天
Hello, evan.
你好  埃文
Evan, this is susan.
埃文  这是苏珊
She's your sister julie's mother.
是朱莉姐姐的妈妈
We used to be married. she was a lot younger then.
我们以前结过婚  那时她还很年轻哦
Evan, why don't you head into the classroom?
埃文  你先进教室吧
I need to talk to your daddy,
我需要和你爸爸谈谈
And i may need to use some grown-up words.
可能会用上些成人用语
Okay, susie q., what's wrong?
好吧  可爱的苏苏  什么事
Get it off that chest you wouldn't let me enhance.
少扣一个扣子也迷不倒我的
Listen, it's bad enough
挺好了  本来在走廊
That i've got one ex-husband running around the halls.
偶遇前夫已经够糟了
I don't need the faculty and the parents
我可不希望同事和孩子的父母知道
Knowing that i have two.
我有两个前夫
So not a word about us having been married.
对我们以前的事情只字不许提
No more wisecracks. no susie q's.
别再说俏皮话  别再叫可爱的苏苏
I am miss susan, art teacher.
叫我苏珊老师  艺术老师
Yes, miss susan.
是的  苏珊老师
Can i bang your erasers after class?
下课后能不能拍拍你的"橡皮擦"
Karl, i'm serious. don't mess with me.
卡尔  我说真的  别和我胡闹
I have a yardstick, and i'm not afraid to use it.
我手里有教鞭  而且我会用
We're gonna be making a presentation
原本为莫里森的合同做的报告
For the morrison contract sooner than we planned.
现在必须提前进行
There are a lot of firms gunning for this,
有很多家公司都在虎视眈眈
And--damn it, lynette! don't--don't touch my figurines.
该死的  勒奈德  别碰我的雕像
These are worth more than the house you live in.
它比你现在的房子都值钱
Big deal. so is this coffee mug.
有什么了不起  这咖啡杯也价值连城
All right, we should break for lunch.
好了  我们休息一下用午餐
No. until this deal closes, we work through lunch.
不  除非敲定这个合同  否则午餐时间加班
But as a consolation, we'll also be working nights.
但令人欣闻的是  晚上也要加班
Nights? you really think that's necessary?
晚班  真的有这个必要吗
This is a $10 million deal, carlos. how bad do you want it?
这是一百万美元的合同啊  卡洛斯  不吸引人吗
You heard the woman. we're working nights.
你们都听到了  晚上加班
Um, i have a tiny scheduling conflict.
我晚上有点事
I coach my daughter's basketball team on friday nights.
周五晚上训练我女儿的篮球队
-So if i could--
-如果我
friday nights are now work nights.
周五晚上要加班
If we're successful,
如果能谈成
Those of you on commission stand to do very well.
你们得到的佣金将会相当可观
And those of you who aren't?
这不是你们的职责吗
well, you get to keep your job
好吧  为了保住工作
Which, in this economy, is a bonus all by itself.
在现在的经济形势下  这是唯一的收入来源
All right, let's run down to the deli, grab a sandwich
好吧  我们去快餐店  买几个三明治
And meet back here in five.
五分钟后在这里集合
You.
你
No touching.
别碰我的东西
And, yes, i'll know.
我会知道的
Isn't she fun?
她多幽默啊
Hey, carlos.
卡洛斯
Did i ever tell you
我告诉过你
That tom and i seriously considered you and gaby
我跟汤姆认真的考虑过
For penny's godparents?
想让你跟加布做佩妮的教父母
you're not getting friday's nights off
周五晚上必须加班
Look, i'm not happy about the schedule either.
听着  我晚上也不想加班
- I'm missing my kids, too.
-我也想回家陪孩子
then do something about it.
那做点什么啊
You're the president. put the brakes on lucy.
你是经理  不要让露西那么嚣张
lynette, i hired her
勒奈特  我请她来的
And that's what she's doing. it's good for the company.
这是她的工作  是为了公司好
But she makes people crazy.
可是她把人都逼疯了
Can't you talk to her, get her to dial it down a bit?
你不能跟她谈谈  把时间协调一下吗
i will think about it
我会考虑的
But don't be asking me for favors like this.
可是别总是这样让我帮你
When we're at the office, i'm not your neighbor,
在办公室的时候  我不是你的邻居
I'm not your friend.
不是朋友
I'm your boss. got it?
是你的老板  明白了吗
Oh, by the way,
还有
You and tom are coming over for cocktails on saturday.
你和汤姆周六过来参加鸡尾酒会吗
Oh, yeah. i plan to get drunk and bitch about my boss.
会去  我打算喝的烂醉  说我老板的坏话
I'm sorry, but this is unacceptable.
我很抱歉  可这我不能接受
Do you at least know why he steals?
至少应该知道他为什么会偷东西吧
If there were Some sordid childhood trauma we could blame it on,
是该怪罪某种恶心的童年创伤吗
It would really help me out with the neighbors
这样我跟邻居还好解释一些
oh he knows
他明白的
Dr. bernstein uncovered that my very first session.
伯恩斯坦医生  帮我掩饰了第一次偷窃
Really? and--and yet he keeps charging me.
是吗  那还敢继续收我的钱
So, doctor, what's this "revelation"
那么  医生  你继续跟我收一小时二十美元的
That you've been keeping from me for $200 an hour?
心灵启示是什么
I steal to hurt you.
我偷东西  是想伤害你
Why would you want to hurt me?
为什么想伤害我
Each day for the past year,
去年的每一天
You have, inch by inch,Slice by slice,
你一点一点 一步一步的
Brought me closer to being a eunuch.
把我变成了太监
Would you excuse us for moment?
能让我们单独谈一会吗
This just became a private conversation.
我们想私下谈一下
If i stay, i might be able to help.
如果我留下  也许会有帮助
You wanna help?
你想帮忙
Why don't you go down to the pharmacy in the lobby
那就去大厅的药店
And buy some aspirin?
买点阿司匹林吧
I'm gonna need it.
我会需要的
I don't deserve this.
我不该承受这些
I have been nothing but supportive of you
从你出狱后
Since you got out of jail.
我全心全意的支持你
I even gave you a job.
还给了你份工作
I wanted to be your partner.
我想做你的合伙人
You made me an employee.
你把我当雇员
So you decided to punish me by resorting to petty theft?
所以你就要偷东西来惩罚我吗
For god sakes, orson, i'm your wife.
看在上帝的份上  奥森  我是你的妻子
Perhaps, but i'm not your husband.
也许是吧  可我不是你丈夫
We may share a bed, but you save your passion for your company
我们虽然同床共枕  你却把激情都给了公司
-That's not true!
-不是这样的
isn't it?
不是吗
Every day for the past year,
过去的一年里
i have been in the background,an afterthought,
我一直不露面  一直在追悔
While you spend day and night nurturing your business.
而你在尽心尽力的经营公司
All the while thinking i had your support.
我一直以为你很支持我
I tried.
我试过了
I thought i wouldn't mind being mr. bree van de kamp.
我想我不介意做布里·范德坎普先生
But it's killing me.
可是这让我痛不欲生
Every day, i get smaller and smaller.
每一天  我变的越来越渺小
And if something doesn't change,
如果就这样继续下去
Orson hodge is just gonna disappear altogether.
奥森·霍吉会完全消失
Girls are out like a light. thanks for dinner.
丫头们睡的很快  晚餐很可口
Carlos, do you have to go back to work?
卡洛斯  你一定要去加班吗
gaby, i get meeting
加布  我要去开会
-But can't lucy cover it?
-露西不能开吗
you know those two
你知道
extras zeroes at my paycheck You like so much?
你喜欢我多挣点钱
they're there because i'm president.
之所以能挣那么多  因为我是经理
Hours are part of the gig.
鱼与熊掌不可兼得
Hey. how about a quickie?
我们速战速决如何
Babe, i don't have time.
宝贝  我没时间
Right, that's why i didn't suggest a longie. oh, come on.
是啊  所以我没说要来场持久战啊
I'll have your eyes rolling back in your head
三分钟之内
In three minutes flat.
我能让你爽翻天
You wanna do it there in front of the kid's cups?
你想在孩子们的宝宝杯前做吗
All gone.
搞定了
Now let's do this. it'll be like old times.
咱们做吧  就像过去那样
We never did it on the table.
我们从没在桌子上做过
Yeah, we did, years ago. don't you remember?
几年前的事了  我们做过的  你忘了吗
I don't think that was me.
那应该不是我
Oh. right.
哦  是啊
Well, we'll create new table memories.
好吧  咱们制造点关于桌子的新回忆吧
If you're trying to turn me on, you just failed miserably.
要是你想挑起我的性趣  你刚彻底失败了
Carlos, do you realize since bradley died
卡洛斯你发现没  布拉德利死后
And you took over, we haven't had sex once?
你接手公司以来  我们一次也没做过了
I miss you. i wanna spend time with you.
我很想你  我想和你在一起
Now move the creamed corn and do me!
快把奶油玉米移开  跟我做爱
okay, how about tomorrow night?
好吧  明晚如何
Yeah, i've heard that before,
这话我听过
And then tomorrow comes, and you're too tired.
明日复明日  明天你又累了
Okay, then, this weekend. i'll be all yours.
好吧  那就这周末  我整个人都交给你
And we can defile any piece of furniture you want.
你想玷污哪件家具都没问题
Hey, karen, you don't have any fax paper, do you?
凯伦  你有传真纸吗
Fax paper!
传真纸
Turn down the dean martin!
把狄恩·马丁那歌声音调小点
Don't worry about it.
别管了
I'll go to the store tomorrow. do you need anything?
我明天去商店一趟  你要什么吗
Eggs... milk...
鸡蛋  牛奶
Lightbulbs...
灯泡
Okay, let's make this easier.
好吧  咱们把事情简单化
Is there anything you don't need?
有什么你不要的吗
I'll tell you what.
跟你说吧
I'll call you from the store in the morning, okay?
明天我到了店里再给你打电话  好吗
What a lovely rainbow, june.
多漂亮的彩虹啊  琼
Here's a gold star for you.
给你一颗小金星
Oh, drew, wow!
德鲁  哇
You know, elephants don't have wings,
要知道  大象是没有翅膀的
But i like the way you're thinking.
不过我喜欢你的创意
Hey, evan, what did you draw?
埃文  你画了什么啊
Um... that's a lot of red.
有很多红色啊
It's blood.
是血
Okay.
好吧
So...
那么
That man must be a doctor
这男的一定是医生了
Making the bloody man all better?
他在给流血的人治伤  对吧
No, he's stabbing him in the guts with a sword.
不  他在用刀捅他  捅进内脏里
Evan, that's...
埃文  这画
Kind of a scary picture.
有点儿吓人
Nuh-unh, it's funny.
不啊  很好笑的
No, honey, it's inappropriate,
不  亲爱的  这画很不合时宜
Especially when the assignment was
特别是对你们的要求
To make a picture that makes you happy.
是画出能让你们感到快乐的东西
This does make me happy.
这确实让我很快乐啊
Where's my gold star?
我的小金星呢
I just can't get used to everyone working--
我就是没法习惯  大家都去工作了
First bree, then susan, now lynette.
一开始是布里  然后是苏珊  现在是勒奈特
Thank god for you.
全拜你所赐
I just had to get out of that boring house.
我才能离开那幢无聊的房子
So what do you gals do when you get together?
-你们姑娘们在一起都干吗
mostly gossip.
主要是聊八卦
Mm. you got any good gossip?
你有什么好八卦吗
Ooh. i heard ed simmons got a harley.
我听说爱德·西蒙斯买了辆哈雷车
You know, i should get back.
知道吗  我该回去了
Come on. give me a break. i'm still new at this. okay.
得了  让我喘口气  我还是新手呢
We'll start with something a little easier--bitching.
我们从简单点儿的开始  发牢骚
I can handle that. bitch away.
这我能搞定  你尽管发
Well, i am so pissed at carlos. he is never home.
我被卡洛斯惹急了  他很少回家
And when he is, he's too tired to do anything.
一回家就什么也不想干
And by "anything," i mean sex.
"什么"我是指做爱
Are you uncomfortable?
你没不舒服吧
A little. go on.
一点点  接着说
Well, we've never had a drought like this.
我们从没像这样过
It's been almost two weeks.
都快两周了
Two weeks? and that's a drought for you?
两周  这对你来说就太久了吗
Yeah. lately, carlos just doesn't want to do it.
是啊  最近卡洛斯就是不想做
Wrong. guys always wanna do it.
你错了  男人总是想做的
Really?
-真的吗
yeah.
是啊
Even if you're tired and get home late?
即便是你很晚才到家  而且很累吗
Even if we're exhausted and late
即便我们很晚到家  精疲力竭
And been shot in the leg... twice.
还在腿上中了两枪
We still want to.
我们还是想做
So you just gotta get past the tired adult to find
所以你只要忽略那个疲惫的成年人
The horny teenage boy inside.
发掘出那个饥渴的青少年就好
Huh. that's good to know.
茅塞顿开
You're good at this girl talk thing.
你很擅长这种女孩子间的聊天嘛
Well, thanks.
好吧  谢了
So, um, does lynette ever talk about me and sex?
那勒奈特说过什么关于我的性话题吗
Yeah, i should get back.
好吧  我该回去了
You called me down here for this?
你叫我来就为这个
It's a kid playing with a soccer ball.
这是一个孩子在踢足球
It's a head, and he's stabbing someone with a sword.
那是个人头  他在用小刀刺别人
Well, maybe it was in self-defense.
也许那是在自卫
Mr. mayer, generally, when kids
梅尔先生  一般来说
exhibit this type of behaviour
孩子出现这样的行为
There's a problem.
是不太正常的
Excuse me.
抱歉
I have to take this. sorry.
我得接个电话  抱歉
Hello?
喂
Thanks for ratting out my kid on his first day.
谢谢你  让我儿子来上课的第一天惨淡收场
It's not my fault. i showed this to the school psychologist.
又不是我的错  我把这画给校心理医生看了
She gave it to the principal. my hands were tied.
是她给校方看的  我没插手这事
so right away it's his fault?
你就武断是他的错吗
Did you ever consider
你想没想过
That he didn't understand the assignment?
也许他是不理解作业的要求呢
I told the class to draw something that made them happy.
我告诉全班  画出让他们感到快乐的画
All the other kids drew kittens and rainbows.
别的孩子画了小猫跟彩虹
Your son drew small intestines on the end of a stick.
你儿子画了棍子后面插着小肠
Let's cut to what this is really about.
咱们打开天窗说亮话吧
You hate me, and you don't want my son in your class.
你恨我  不想我儿子在你班上
That is not true!
-不是这样的
it is, too!
就是这样
You're still punishing me for what happened between us.
为咱俩的事  你还在惩罚我
You're stuck in the past
你一直走不出过去
And blaming me for your screwed-up life!
还把自己一团糟的生活怪在我头上
okay, will someone call Guinness
快来人打给吉尼斯世界记录吧
Because you just set the world record
你刚破了一句话里
For the biggest load of crap in one sentence.
-包含最多屁话的世界纪录
oh, bite me!
去死吧
How long was i gone?
我离开很久了吗
This is nothing, mr. hobson.
没事  霍布森先生
We were just having a difference of opinion.
我们只是意见有点分歧
Yeah, and my opinion is
没错  我的意见就是
Your teacher doesn't understand the difference
你的老师不了解情绪有问题
Between emotional problems and creativity.
-跟创造力之间的差别
shut up, karl.
闭嘴  卡尔
Excuse me. did you just tell him to shut up?
抱歉  你刚才是叫他闭嘴吗
You know, this is typical "susan" behavior.
你知道  这是典型的"苏珊式"举动了
And you wonder why no man can stay with you.
你还奇怪为什么没男人能跟你呆在一起吗
Would this seem any less shocking
要是我告诉你  我们曾经结果12年的婚
If i told you we were once married for 12 years?
是不是能让你少惊讶点
Yes, am i speaking to mr. dinsmore?
是丁斯莫尔先生吗
Ah, this is bree van de kamp.
我是布里·范德坎普
Yes, it's nice to talk to you, too.
也很高兴跟您聊天
Well, as i'm sure you're aware,
您肯定知道  您的公司
Your company has made several offers to purchase mine.
对我的公司提出过几次收购提案
Yes, i know i said i wasn't interested,
是的  我知道我说过我没兴趣
But some things have happened in my personal life
可我的私人生活发生了一些事情
And i think i'm ready to...
我想  我准备好
Finally make a deal.
跟您交易了
Really?
真的吗
Well, that's wonderful.
那太好了
Why don't you, uh,
不如
Come to my office tomorrow and we'll talk?
明天来我办公室  我们再聊呢
Good-bye, mr. dinsmore.
再见  丁斯莫尔先生
There you go. the rest is yours.
得了  剩下的是你的
Thanks. i don't know what it is.
谢了  我不知道这是怎么了
Every time i go to the market, there's stuff i forget.
每次我去商店  总能忘买东西
I know what it is. you're old.
我知道怎么回事  你老了
So where's dave?
-戴夫在哪呢
camping.
宿营去了
Ooh,camping. how fun.
宿营  多有趣啊
Enjoying the great outdoors,
享受户外的美好时光
getting a bunch of teenage kids to get a weekend
跟孩子们一起度周末
Good for him.
对他很好啊
Look, I know that you think  he's some creepy psycho.
听着  我知道你觉得他是个乖僻的神经病
But you should know that he has had a very hard life,
可你得知道  他过去有段痛苦的经历
An there are things about him that you don't understand.
关于他的事  有些你不了解
Like what?
比如呢
He was married before
他过去结过婚
And his wife died in an accident
他妻子死于一场车祸
Along with their 3-year-old daughter.
同时遇难的  还有他三岁的女儿
Oh, edie. are you sure?
伊迪  你确定吗
Yes.
是的
So if at times
所以要是有时
His behavior seems a little strange,
他的行为举止有点奇怪
Try to remember the grief he's carrying.
试着想想他背负的伤痛
You know, i lost a kid.
你知道  我也失去过一个孩子
It does things to you.
确实会对人产生影响的
No wonder he...
怪不得他
Oh, god, i wish i'd known.
上帝啊  真希望我早点知道
Well, you do now.
你现在知道了
So next time, try to be a little more understanding.
下次遇见他  试着善解人意一点
Of course.
当然了
You know, i could use a drink.
你知道  我想喝杯酒
Come to my house and we'll crank up dean martin and...
来我家吧  我们听点狄恩·马丁
Toss a few back.
再拌拌嘴啥的
Come on.
来吧
Mom?
妈
Oh, andrew. i didn't hear you come in.
安德鲁  我没听见你进来了
That dinsmore guy is waiting for you downstairs.
那个叫丁斯莫尔的正在楼下等你
Thank you, dear.
谢谢你  亲爱的
I must say, bree. i was surprised to get your call.
我得说  布里  接到你电话我很惊讶
You've always said you'd never sell your company.
你总说  你不可能会卖你公司的
Bree has decided she wants more family time.
布里觉得自己想跟家人多点时间相处
She's a very traditional woman, you know.
她是个很传统的女性  你知道
It's one of the reasons i fell in love with her.
这也是我和她坠入爱河的原因之一
Does that mean you're going to stop working altogether?
你是说你完全不打算工作了吗
I know your fans have been hoping for a second book,
我知道你的粉丝一直在盼你出下本书呢
Uh, my wife included.
我的太太也是哦
That's sweet, but i've decided to focus
那太好了  可我决定把精力集中在
On other pursuits at the moment.
其他方面
Mm, yes, her sole ambition now is to be Mrs. Orson Hodge.
她目前唯一的事业就是做好奥森·霍吉太太
And at the risk of sounding selfish,
听起来有点自私
I'm glad i'll be the only one she's cooking for.
我很高兴  以后她只为我一人做饭
Were you able to look over the contracts I sent?
你看过我发过来的合同了吗
Oh shoot! I left them upstairs.
我把它们放在楼上了
I'll show you the offices before we start the demolition.
我带你看看办公室吧  办公室就要拆了
You're getting rid of your office?
办公室你也不要了
No, we don't need it anymore,
是  我们不再需要了
And bree knows i've always wanted a game room.
而且布里知道我一直想要个娱乐室
So it's your "sole ambition" to be mrs. orson hodge?
这是你"唯一的事业"吗  做好奥森·霍吉太太
Andrew.
安德鲁
No, i-i have to ask.
我还是要问
Why are you letting orson sell your company?
你为什么要让奥森卖掉你的公司
It was my idea.
那是我的主意
My work has been compromising my marriage.
我的工作已经危害到我的婚姻
I didn't realize the toll it's been taking on orson.
我没意识到影响到了奥森
Okay, so he's unhappy.
好吧  所以他不太开心
Buy him some golf clubs, put him on lithium,
让他去打打高尔夫  吃点治郁闷的药
But don't give up everything you've worked so hard for.
但你不能放弃你辛苦挣来的这一切
Andrew, do you know why my book sold so well?
安德鲁  你知道我的书为什么卖得那么好
Because it was authentic.
因为这书写的都是真实的
I actually believe in The old-fashioned values i wrote about.
正如同我写的  我一直坚信那些传统价值
I believe in men opening doors for ladies
我认定  男人应该要为女人开门
And children respecting their elders.
孩子们应该尊重长辈
I also believe that sometimes
我也相信有时候
Women need to make sacrifices for their husbands.
女人要为丈夫作出牺牲
I would be the worst kind of hypocrite
如果我宣扬这种价值
If i preached these values
自己却无法履行
And then didn't follow them myself.
那我就是最差的伪君子了
Okay, i get it. you love orson,
我明白了  你爱奥森
And you're willing to sell your company to prove it.
你愿意卖掉公司来证明这点
What i'm wondering is, if he loves you,
我想  如果他爱你
Why would he want you to stop doing what makes you happy?
那他干嘛非要你放弃热爱的事业
Hey. you busy?
你好  在忙吗
What is it?
什么事情
I brought you a little gift.
我给你带来个小礼物
Oh. cute.
哦  很可爱
I thought it would be a nice addition to your collection.
我想  它会让你的收藏锦上添花
I knew it was you.
我知道是你
Pardon?
啥
You're the one who complained about me to carlos.
你跟卡洛斯抱怨过我
I'm... not sure what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么
Oh, jeez. what, you knife me in the back,
天哪  你在背后放冷箭
And now you're gonna play stupid?
现在又来装天真
Carlos said some people are having problems with me
卡洛斯说有人对我有意见
And that i should watch my demeanor.
我应该注意自己的行为
And i thought to myself, who are "some people"?
我就想  究竟是谁
And then it hit me-- it's the chummy neighbor.
突然我想到了  一定是那个友好的邻居
Okay, yes, carlos and i spoke briefly,
是的  我和卡洛斯说了几句
- But i thought he blew me off.
-但我想卡洛斯有点夸大
so that's your defense?
这是你的解释吗
You thought your backstabbing was unsuccessful?
你觉得背后陷害的策略失败了
Well, i'll admit it's kind of flimsy,
我承认是有点弱
But until i got something better...
等我想到更好的点子
Okay, next time you have an issue with me,
下次对我再有意见
You know where my office is.
直接来我办公室提
Oh, and, uh, as far as friday nights are concerned...
至于周五晚上加班的事情
Consider that a permanent work night.
以后每周五晚上固定加班
Don't worry.
别担心
If you're as bad at coaching as you are at office politics,
如果你的教育和你的办公室阴谋一样烂的话
Your daughter won't be missing much.
你女儿也没错过什么
Found the contract.
合同拿到了
Everything is in order.
所有事情都安排好了
All we need now is your signature.
我们只差签字了
Mr. Dinsmore,
丁斯莫尔先生
If i speak to my husband for a moment?
如果你不介意我想和我丈夫说两句
Oh, yeah, please, go ahead. i'll--i'll be right outside.
好  我就在外面
What's wrong?
怎么了
This is happening so fast.
这一切都发生的太快了
Yes, a bit. but it was your idea.
是有一点  但这是你的主意
Well, i have a new idea.
我现在有个新想法
I'd like to wait.
我想等等看
Wait? but i-i need this for my recovery.
等  我需要这个帮助我治疗
Just give me one year. that's not asking too much, is it?
就给我一年的时间  不过分吧
You made me a promise. you need to stick to it.
你答应过我  你必须完成
Orson, think about how i built this company from nothing,
奥森  想想看  我白手起家  创建这家公司
How it brings me joy and pride
这家公司让我感到我快乐  自豪
and a sense of accomplishment
还有成就感
Is that really something you want me to give up?
你真的想让我放弃这一切吗
Yes.
是的
Mr. Dinsmore, would you come back in, please?
丁斯莫尔先生  请进来吧
So are we ready?
好了吗
Actually, no.
不
I'm not selling.
我不卖了
Excuse me?
什么
Tell your wife
告诉你妻子
I will be doing that second book after all.
我还打算再出第二本书
Well, i'm--i'm sorry to hear that.
太遗憾了
Bree...
布里
What about my problem?
我怎么办
I might start stealing again.
我可能还会去偷东西
Steal what you must, my love.
偷吧  亲爱的
But it won't be my company.
但别想动我的公司
Look at him.
看他
He's out like a light already.
他已经睡着了
That's what a long day of fishing does to you.
他今天钓了一整天的鱼
Yeah, well, he's gonna need all of his energy
他需要养精蓄锐
For our big hike tomorrow, right?
明天好好爬山
Actually, i don't think i'm gonna go with you guys.
我可能不能跟你们去了
My knee's been kind of bothering me.
我的膝伤发作
Okay, well, then why don't we wait till the next day
那我们就延迟一天
And see how you feel?
等你好一些
No, no, it's fine. i'm just gonna hang out here.
没事  你们去好了  我就在这等你们
Besides, it's such a romantic hike.
而且两个人爬山应该很浪漫吧
You guys should do it alone.
你们应该单独去
You always have such a good attitude.
你总是这么体贴
- Do i?
-是吗
uh-huh.
是
It seems like you take everything in stride, you know?
你总是从容不迫地对待所有事情
Like you just naturally find the silver lining.
你总是很自然地就看到好的一面
Yeah, i wish it were natural.
是啊  我希望是自然的
I had to teach myself to be this way.
我一直告诉自己这样做
With some of the stuff that's happened to me,
发生过一些事情
I never would've survived if i hadn't.
如果我不这样做  我可能活不下去
So what's your secret?
你的秘密是什么
Oh, i realized that...
我意识到
I was waiting for somebody to fix things.
我一直在等着有人能帮我
But no one was going to.
但没人来帮我
It was all up to me.
只能靠我自己
I had to decide what was important
我不得不决定什么是最重要的
And go after it.
并为之努力
I had to make myself happy.
我要让自己开心
Are you Happy?
那你现在开心了吗
I'm gettin' there.
就快了
Why don't you get some sleep?
你为什么不去休息一会
You got a big day tomorrow.
明天会很累
Come on, lucy. why would you agree to this meeting?
露西  你为什么要开这个会
Well, we're overextended as it is.
我们已经过度扩张业务了
Fine.
好吧
I will see on the conference on 7:00 a.m.
七点会上见
Hi there.
亲爱的
Hey, babe.
嗨  亲爱的
What are you doing up?
你起来干什么
I couldn't sleep. i was a little hot.
我睡不着  我觉得有点热
That's better.
这样好多了
You look a little warm yourself.
你看起来也有点热
Okay, i know where you're going
我想你干什么
Your pants would be around your ankles right now
现在你的裤子应该脱到脚踝
gaby, what are you doing
加布  你要干什么啊
I'm releasing the horny teen inside of you.
我来释放你的激情
- Now come on. two boobs, no waiting.
-来吧  不要等了
damn it, gaby,
该死  加布
I thought we were gonna wait till the weekend. i'm tired
说好等到周末的  我累死了
it is not my problme
不是我的问题
Actually, it is! you know, if big carlos is tired,
也是你的问题  大卡洛斯累了
That pretty much rules out little carlos, too.
小卡洛斯就没精神
Now listen up, the pair of you.
那你们两个都听好了
I haven't been sitting around in butt floss all night
为我的健康着想  我可不想穿内裤过夜
For my health. you're putting out.
你来解决这个
That's more like it!
我更喜欢这样
Well, i'm awake now.
我现在醒了
In fact...
事实上
Mind if we spice it up a bit?
不如我们来点火辣的
I forgot these were in the nightstand.
我都忘了他们放在床头柜
This is gonna be fun.
一定很有趣
Mm-hmm. there. how's that?
感觉如何
- Tight, just the way i like it.
-很紧  我喜欢
me, too.
我也是
Good night.
晚安
Carlos, where you going?
卡洛斯你去哪
To go grab a few hours sleep Before i have to get back to work.
抓紧睡个几小时  然后继续工作
Carlos, get back here! carlos!
卡洛斯  回来  卡洛斯
Could you at least scratch my nose?!
至少帮我抓抓鼻子
Amy, that is very sweet.
艾米  很可爱
I love the colors you used.
我喜欢你用的颜色
Oh, danielle, that is just beautiful.
丹妮尔  这很漂亮
Evan, that is very pretty.
埃文  这很好看
You did the assignment just like i asked. good job!
你完成我要求的作业  干得好
That's not mine.
这不是我的
Annie asked me to bring hers up for her.
安妮让我帮她交
This one's mine.
下面那张是我的
Don't wake him up.
别吵醒他
I know. ow! come on.
我知道  走吧
I know.
我知道
What is that? let's just go back. let's go back.
那边是什么  咱们回去
I heard a gunshot. it sounded like a hunting rifle.
我听见枪响  是来福枪
- Yeah, it almost hit katherine.
-差点打中凯瑟琳
you guys all right?
你们还好吗
- Yeah, i think so.
-我没事
hey, this is a state park.
这是国家公园
People aren't supposed to be hunting here. well,
没人在这打猎
i guess these guys don't care about that
我想那些打猎的不在乎这些
- I just wanna get out of here. please?
-咱们离开这吧
yeah, of course.
好  当然
We'll, uh, go back and pack, and we'll leave.
回去收拾行囊  然后咱们就离开
Well, sorry, man.
对不住  伙计
Me, too.
我也很遗憾
Juanita! celia! get your coats on!
胡安妮塔  西利娅  穿好衣服
We're going to see daddy.
我们去找爸爸
- Let me see it.
-让我看看
okay, just so you know,
好的  你知道
I should be bringing this to the psychologist.
我可以直接把它交给心理学家的
But I didn't, because this kind of "self-expression"
但我没有  考虑到你所谓的个人看法
- Usually gets aid expelled.
-不利于解决问题
just let me see it.
拿来吧
Aw, hell.
该死
Yeah, "aw, hell."
对啊  该死
You got a problem here, karl.
你遇上麻烦了
Your son's got some serious anger issues,
你儿子内心充满了愤怒
And you need to figure out what's going on.
你需要去了解他在想些什么
I know what's going on. this is his mom.
我知道是怎么回事  这是他妈妈
Marisa?
玛丽莎
Well, why would he draw a picture of her like this?
那他为什么把她画成这样
She left us... six weeks ago.
她六周前离开我们了
Karl...
卡尔
I woke up one day
有天我醒来
To find her standing there with her bags packed.
看见她收拾好行李站在那里
She said she was overwhelmed,
她说她受够了
That she loved Evan
她爱埃文
But she wasn't cut out to be a mother.
但她不适合做妈妈
So she just left?
她就一走了之了?
So here i am, alone,
什么都得靠我了
Raising this boy.
抚养他长大
And it's obvious i'm not doing a very good job.
显然我不是个好父亲
You must be loving this.
你很高兴看见我这样吧
Why?
怎么这么说?
'cause i did the exact same thing to you.
因为我也曾这样对你
You know, i can understand why you react the way you do
现在我能理解为什么再见到我时
When you bump into me,
你会有那样的反应
Why it bothers you.
你为什么那么生气
I never really got it until just now.
现在我总算明白了
I use to hope that one day,
我过去常希望
You would know what this felt like,
你能体会到我的心情
And now that you do...
这一天终于来了
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
-Oh! hey, lynette! -hi!
-嗨 勒奈特
Great office. i see you're busy. don't let me disturb you.
办公室真漂亮  我知道你在忙  不打扰你工作
I just wanted to drop off the girls
她们就呆一会
So i could talk to carlos for a sec.
我有事找卡洛斯
All right, girls, have fun with aunt lynette.
好的  孩子们  好好玩
You think you can buy me off with presents?
你想用礼物收买我?
gaby, now is not a good time
加布  你来的不是时候
Well, i'd say let's talk about it tonight,
是啊  我应该说  好吧  我们晚上再谈
But who knows if you're even gonna come home?
但天知道你回不回来
Damn it, gaby.
该死
You're the one that pushed me take this job.
你逼我接手这份工作
And ever since i did,
我照做了
All you've done is complain about how hard i'm working.
但换来的是你不停的抱怨
You're right, and i'm sorry. it's just... i'm scared.
对不起  你是对的  我只是...害怕
We're turning into what we used to be.
我们会重蹈覆辙
I'm unhappy at home,
我在家不开心
You're always working, trying to buy me off wh presents,
而你每天都工作  然后买礼物敷衍我
Too tired to make me feel loved.
到了最后  对感情都倦了
We've made these mistakes before, carlos.
卡洛斯  我们错过
For god sakes, let's not make 'em again.
看在上帝的份上  我们不要再这么做了
I made a commitment here, gaby.
我同意  加布
I don't think i can just bail.
但我现在不能抽身
I know you can't,
我知道你不能
And that's the part that really scares me.
所以我才那么怕
We're bored.
好无聊啊
Hey, i got you sodas, didn't i?
我不是给你们拿饮料了吗?
And i let you feed the paper shredder.
还让你们喂了碎纸机
- Don't you have any toys?
-没有玩具吗
No. i got a hole puncher.
没有  不过我有一个打孔机
Sorry. that's the best i could do. come on.
对不起  我只有这些了  来
What about those glass things?
我们能玩那些小玻璃吗
They're pretty. can i hold one?
好漂亮  我可以摸一下吗
Oh, sweetie, those aren't to play with,
亲爱的  它们不是拿来玩的
Not unless you wanna see someone go completely bonkers.
除非你想看某人疯掉
Actually, they do look like a lot of fun.
它们看起来太好玩了
If only i had the power to stop you...
我怎能阻止你们
What the hell are you doing?!
你们在干什么
We're playing. what does it look like?
在玩啊  要不你觉得我们在干什么
Are these your kids?
是你的小孩吗
'cause they were in my office playing with my figurines,
她们在我办公室玩我的小雕像
Which are imported. they're worth a lot of dinero.
那些可是非常值钱  意义重大的东西
Do you even understand what i'm saying?!
你知道我在说什么吗
- What's with the yelling?
-她在吼什么
i don't know.
不知道
i'm just here as you are
我也才看见
Look, let me boil it down for you.
好 让我说得更明白一些
Office, si!
工作  可以
Day care? no!
日托  不行
Lucy, what's going on?
露西  发生什么事了
Apparently, some people don't understand
显然一些人不知道
That this is a place of business,
这是工作的地方
And they need to keep their kids at home!
不是带小孩的地方
Then i guess you should yell at me.
那你应该把怒气撒向我
- These are my kids.
-她们是我的小孩
Come here, sweetie.
亲爱的  过来
I, uh, I didn't know that.
我不知道
I...I thought they were hers 'cause they're...
我以为是她的孩子  因为她们...
Could you just go?
走吧
I'm sorry.
对不起
So what if they were?
如果她们不是我的小孩
- That's the way you talk to people?
-你就会那么粗鲁吗
i said i'm sorry.
我道过歉了
Look, I-I am trying so hard to make this deal happen.
我花了太多精力在生意上
I guess the stress is just getting to me.
我想我压力太大了
It's getting all of us. Maybe it's a sign
每个人都有压力  也许这件事正好
We should change the way we do things around here.
说明我们需要改变一下我们做事的方式
We are trying to play with the big boys, carlos.
我们正在努力和大公司竞争
Now is not the time to pull back.
现在放弃是不明智的
Don't you want this company to succeed?
你不想公司成功吗
I wanna build a company that treats its people well
我建立的公司人与人之间是友好的
And lets them go home at night to see their families.
他们每晚可以回家  和家人在一起
Look, i know i don't have the greatest beside manner.
我知道我的脾气不太好
But you hired me to take this company to number one.
你雇我是让我帮你打造一间最好的公司
Now if you don't want to do that,
如果你后悔了
I'm probably not your girl.
我或许不适合和你共事
I was just thinking the same thing.
我也这么想的
What happened to you?
你怎么了
The old carlos would do anything to be the best.
以前的你凡事都争第一
I guess i'm not the old carlos anymore.
今非昔比了
Fine.
好吧
Don't forget your little animals!
别忘了拿走你的小动物们
Orson, please come upstairs.
奥森  和我上楼吧
I know what that couch does to your back.
睡沙发对你的背不好
Don't worry about me. i'll be fine.
别担心我  我没事
I Know you're disappointed right now, but you have to know,
我知道你现在很失望  但你必须知道
I really do want to find some way for you to be happy.
我确实想要让你快乐
So do I.
我也是
Hey, don't you want your stuff?
你不把东西拿回去
Oh, can I get it tomorrow? I just really want to get home.
我明天来拿  行吗?  我想快点回家
Edie?
伊迪?
I always wondered
我经常在想
Why you were so determined to live on wisteria lane.
你为什么就这么想在紫藤郡生活
You said you thought we'd be happy here,
你说过我们会在这里生活得很幸福
And I wanted to believe you.
我试过去相信你
But it turned out that you...
但事实上你只是
Just wanted to be close to Mike Delfino.
想接近麦克·德尔非诺
Who gave you that?
谁给你的
Nobody gave it to me.
没人给我
I did research. You think i'm too stupid to do research?
我做过调查  你不会觉得我笨到连这也不会吧
Edie, listen. this doesn't mean anything.
伊迪  这说明不了什么
It's all there--the accident, mike's acquittal,
上面什么都写了  意外  麦克无罪释放
And even a little mention of how...
还提到...
David dash
大卫是如何难过
Couldn't make it to the funeral
甚至不能去参加葬礼
Because he had a nervous breakdown.
因为他精神崩溃了
Honey, look.
听我说  亲爱的
Just give me a chance to explain.
听我解释
Oh, so now you want to explain?
你现在想解释了
Okay, why don't you start
好  那就先解释为什么
By explaining why you married me?
想和我结婚吧
I married you because i love you.
因为我爱你
No! you married me because you needed a cover story
不是  你和我结婚只是想掩饰
So you could get close to the man who killed your family.
这样你就能接近害你家破人亡的凶手
That's ridiculous.
荒谬
Yeah, it's insane.
是啊  太疯狂了
But that's why you did it.
但这是事实
So what are you gonna do now?
你接下来的计划是什么
You gonna hurt him?
去伤害他吗
I mean...
我的意思是...
You know, that's the only.
那是唯一
Logical explanation.
符合逻辑的解释
And my only question is...
我只是想知道
What the hell have you been waiting for?
你还在等什么
Honey, you're not feeling well.
亲爱的  你可能不舒服了
Let's get you upstairs into bed.
我们上去休息了吧
Tell me the truth, you freak.
变态佬  告诉我事实
Did you move us here to hurt mike delfino?
你来这里就是为了干掉麦克·德尔非诺吗
He destroyed...
他毁掉了...
Everything i ever loved,
我至爱的一切
And he was never punished.
他从来没有得到惩罚
I need to make things right.
我要主持公道
Why?
为什么
Why did you have to do this?
为什么你要这么做
We could've been so happy.
我们本可以很幸福的
What are you doing?
你要干什么
I'm gonna tell him before you...
我要告诉他
- Before you do something stupid.
-我不要你做傻事
Edie, don't.
伊迪  不要
Give me that.
把它给我
No! aah!
不
Get out of here! just get the hell out!
滚出去  给我滚出去
I'm calling the police! do you hear me?
我要报警了  听到没
Yes, life is full of nasty shocks.
生活中总是充满了令人震惊的事
And they always seem to occur
这一些事情
When we least expect them.
往往不请自来
And once our system has been jolted,
一旦我们的身体遭遇此事
The question becomes, will we survive?
问题就来了  我们会幸存下来吗